# Paidamoyo - Janet Azehko

E-Mail Me! LinkedIn GitHub

I am a former circus performer, current fashion design student and self taught web developer seeking a career in tech that suits my professional skills, ability to quickly learn new things, and my love of finding creative ways to look at the world. My decade-long career as an artist and performer gives me the unique ability to find creative and empathetic solutions to every problem. I can bring creativity, drive, and passion to your organization.

#### **Education**

#### Lambda School

Summer Hackers Program Summer 2018

### City College of San Francisco

Certificate of Achievement Web Application Programming

**Associates of Art** Fashion Design (Spring 2022)

## **Academy of Art University**

**Bachelors of Art** Fashion Product Development (TBD)

#### **Skills**

### Web Development:

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React

**Tools:** Visual Studio Code, Git, GitHub, Chrome Developer Tools, NPM, Boostrap, LESS, Node, js, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Loom

# **Project Management:**

- Scheduling
- Event Production
- Budgeting
- Conflict Management

# Fashion Design:

Patternmaking Sewing Illustration

### Experience

### Kinfolq

Community Manager 4/2021 - Current

#### Remote

- Provide engaging text, image and video content for all social media and professional accounts.
- Set plan and implement social media and communication campaigns and strategies.
- Monitor, track and report on feedback and online reviews.
- · Organize and manage events to boost brand awareness and consumer engagement.
- Respond to members in a timely manner.
- Build relationships with customers, industry professionals and potential members.
- Stay up-to-date with trends in tech and venture capital.

# Concept SF Inc

Lead Editor 1/2018- Current

#### Remote

Review submitted posts and decide which ones to accept and reject.

- Edit posts for clarity, grammar and match for style and tone.
- Write or modify content to maximize post quality, reader interest, and social media referrals.
- Ensure that blog posts go to clients in a timely manner.
- Develop proposals for achieving goals and targets, including increasing readership and content engagement.
- Execute on planned strategies to achieve set targets while ensuring quality remains high. Use metrics and data to measure progress.
- Cultivate and support volunteer contributions to ensure a dependable, diverse group of content creators.
- Lead meetings to plan editorial content for upcomming projects.

#### **Code Crew**

Teacher's Assistant 3/2021 - Current

#### Memphis, TN (remote)

- Work with lead teacher to monitor class attendance.
- Revise lesson material with students individually or in small groups.
- Collaborate with lead teachers to recognize issues students are facing and recommend solutions.
- Grade student's assignments using online grading system.
- Document student progress and communicate with staff.
- Ensure a safe online learning environment.

# Grabango

Quality Trainer 1/2019 - 10/2019

#### Berkeley, CA

- · Helped teams collect, clean and label data and images.
- Identified and categorized objects in images and videos.
- · Annotated actions in images and videos.
- Used various sets of rules to process data sets, logged exceptions as they occurred.

#### **Tech Inclusion**

Social Media Volunteer 1/2016 - 10/2019

#### San Francisco, CA

- Plan and execute social media campaigns for events in New York San Francisco, London, Melbourne and others both nationally and internationally.
- Successfully implemented a new video interview component to Social Media that increased follower engagement.
- Managed social media accounts with over 3,000 followers.

#### **Kinetic Arts Center**

Administrative Assistant 6/2018 - 3/2019

### Oakland, CA

- · Managed front desk, including telephones, mail/messages, faxes and visitors.
- Reviewed and entered class enrollment into MindBody software system.
- Registered new clients and assist with purchases of class packages and merchandise.
- Provided correspondence for customer concerns in person, by phone and email.
- Managed community donations on behalf of Kinetic Arts.

# **Living Dream Arts**

Instructor 2/2018 - 2/2019

#### Berkeley, CA

- Managed and developed curriculum for teaching circus skills to children K-6.
- Raised money for new apparatus for students.
- · Expanded program to include more students from a disadvantaged background.

### **Project Erostribe**

Creative Director 1/2010-Current

### San Francisco, CA

• Supervised project collaborations with internationally recognized recording artists such as Shpongle and Ott, World Bodypaint Champions such as Trina Merry and Matteo Arfanotti and companies such as Google and Microsoft.

- Directed art projects for events such as Re: Creation San Francisco, Burning Man 2017, Hot Couture
- Raised over \$40,000 in private funds.
- Managed social media accounts totaling 20K in followers.



© 2021 GitHub, Inc. Terms Privacy Security Status Docs Contact GitHub Pricing API Training Blog About Loading complete